## Zidan Putra Rahman

Email : zidanputrarahman153@gmail.com

Portfolio : zidanputra.my.id Github : github.com/zidan-p Phone : 081359137982

LinkedIn : linkedin.com/in/zidan-putra-rahman-546b6b232/

#### **About Me**

Web Developer who masters various fields of web development. Have some experience and knowledge in the field of Web Development. Familiar with React as frontend framework and Express as Backend Framework. Using Nodejs as a tool for software development in daily life. Always work with passion and responsibility.

# **Skills and Competencies**

Reactjs, Redux, Nestjs, Nextjs, MongoDb, MySql, Nodejs, Express, Tailwind, Laravel, Java, HTML, CSS, JS, PHP, Typescript

# **Experiences**

### PT Digitalisasi Global Inklusif

July 2023 – Now

### **Freelance Fullstack Developer**

- Add some feature to App fixransomware
- Fix various bug wich in frontend or backend of App fixransomeware
- Itegrate monggodb database to the app and handle query monthly statistic in admin view

## Disminfosandi Banyuwangi

July 2022 – November 2022

#### **Intern Developer**

- Create company profile website for Diskominfosandi Banyuwangi using laravel
- Design and build guiz game with websocket integration.

#### **Education**

# **SMKS Telkom Sandhy Putra Malang**

2020 - 2023

software engineering graduate (87,8 / 100)

### **Projects**

#### Web Profile

My personal web profile. Contains my collection of certificate and project

- Build using nestjs and typescript with feature based architecture
- Use framer motion for animating common transition

## Wikusama Hotel

Hotel management and booking application with the application of booking transaction logic

- Multi role which are Guest and Admin. Admin page with access to manage room, room type, transaction etc
- Build using Nextjs framework for frontend and Express for backend

### **Diskominfosandi Company Profile**

Dynamic company profile website for Diskominfosandi

- Build using Laravel
- Multi role for Admin dan Guest, with Admin Access to manage for Berita, Video Profile, Photo Profile dan organization structure